usnpl.com 2006-06-20

# US Newspaper Links Privacy Policy

**US Newspaper Links Privacy Policy**

US Newspaper Links (USNPL) is committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information. 

**Consumer Information**

USNPL does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address when you visit our Web site. However, when you volutarily fill out and submit a form on our Web site, USNPL may obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). This information is used to better understand what types of systems are used to view our site and what, if any, technical changes are needed in our site. 

Advertisers on USNPL do not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address in the process of delivering ads. However, they do obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by advertisers is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of their advertisers. 

US Newspaper Links [home](http://www.usnpl.com/)
